(忆往昔)
你不能就这么看着我  对我说你没事
You can't just look me in the face and tell me you're fine.
你失眠  还大量饮酒
You're not sleeping, you drink for the record.
跟我说实话
Just be honest with me.
你这副样子
How are those the actions of someone
怎么可能分清是非
who knows they did the right thing?
你对我撒谎  杀了我的朋友
You lied to me, and you killed my friend.
杀死艾米可没错
Killing Amy was not wrong.
你下不了手  所以我来
You couldn't do it, so I did.
我现在甚至不能跟你呆在一起
You know, I can't even be around you right now.
你不如忍耐一下跟我一起搞定这件事
You might as well bite the bullet and work with me on this one.
我不知道我能不能做到
I don't know if I can.
我的意思是  咱们一起阻止杀戮
I'm just saying, let's try and stop the killings.
那是你的东西
That's your stuff.
是啊  我想我们还是坐一辆车吧
Yeah. Yeah. I figured we'd take one car.
你知道吗  你是对的
Look, you know what? You were right.
艾米的事  我理解你为什么这么做
About amy. I get why you did it.
你只是为了保证没有别人会再受伤害
You were just trying to make sure no one else got hurt.
《凶鬼恶灵》
"Supernatural".
你是说有这么一本书
You're saying this is a book?
不是一本  是一系列
Books. It was a series.
不过卖得不怎么好
Didn't sell a lot of copies, though.
恰克  我是你的头号粉丝
Chuck, I am your number-one fan.
我知道《凶鬼恶灵》只是一本书而已  好吧
But I know that "Supernatural" Is just a book, okay?
-贝基  那些都是真的  -我就知道
- Becky, it's all real. - I knew it!
-女士  你没事吧  -真的是你吗
You okay, lady? Is it really you?
-能否请你不要再摸我了  -不行
- Can you... Quit touching me? - No.
(如今)
(内华达州  拉斯维加斯)
好吧  说出来你肯定不信
Okay, you won't believe it.
别人都以为我这么说  是为了多拿小费
People think I just say it to get a bigger tip.
说来听听
Try me.
好吧  我在读研究生
Fine. I'm in grad school.
瞧  就是这种眼神
See? Okay? There's a look.
别这样
Okay? Stop.
不  这么看你  是因为我喜欢聪明的姑娘
No, this is my "I dig smart chicks" Look.
如果学校里的女生都穿成你这样
Now, if they, uh, if they wore that, I...
我当时就不会辍学了
I wouldn't have dropped out of school.
那么  你有什么心事
So, what's your deal?
心事
My deal?
是啊
Yeah.
你进来时的表情  就好像谁把你家狗杀了似的
You came in here looking like somebody shot your puppy.
现在你下班了  情况也有所好转
Well, things are looking up now that your shift's over.
好吧
All right.
事情是这样的
Uh, here's the deal.
我的一个朋友  他有个弟弟
I have this friend. He's got this younger brother.
脑子有点不正常
Right? Cannon's a little loose.
不久之前  他犯病了
You know, his reactor blew a while back.
情况不太好
It's not good.
我朋友他...他一直在等
My friend -- he's, uh... He's kind of been sitting,
等他弟弟再发疯
waiting to see if he goes guano again.
我猜他弟弟惹麻烦了
And I assume it just hit the fan?
但事实上没有
Well, that's the thing. It didn't.
就一个疯子来说  那孩子现在算是正常了
The kid's all reasonable now, considering he's crazy.
好吧  他...他不是个疯子
Well, he's -- I mean, he's not crazy. He --
他看上去似乎又好转的迹象
He's starting to seem like things might be getting a little better.
那算是件好事吧
Well, that's a good thing, right?
简直就是个奇迹
It's a freakin' miracle.
但是...
Except...
就在他们哥俩...
When it happens during their, uh...
踏上一年一度的维加斯朝圣之旅时
their sacred annual pilgrimage to Vegas...
他却自己一个人去沙漠里
And he goes off on some Granola-munching hike
潇洒地远足去了
in the desert by himself.
他可能只是想一个人静静
Well, maybe he just needs some time alone.
是啊
Yeah.
我们都有需要面对自我的时候
We all need to face ourselves sometime.
他可能确实需要
Maybe he does.
我说的不是他
Wasn't talking about him.
不好意思
Excuse me.
说曹操  曹操到
Speak of the devil.
他离这儿只有四个街区
He's four blocks away?
瞧  弟弟还是需要你的
See? Baby bro needs you after all.
迪恩
Dean.
没事  不需要这个
It's okay. You won't need that.
-快来  -我还以为你
- Come on. - I thought you were out,
与大自然天人合一神马的
uh, becoming one with the land or some crap.
你得...过来
You got to -- come here.
好了
All right.
然后...
Now...
这是什么
What is this?
显然  粉色代表着忠诚
Uh, apparently, uh, pink is for loyalty.
好吧  这是什么情况
All right, so, what's the pretext?
咱们...是婚礼傲客(美国喜剧)吗
What are we -- uh, wedding crashers, huh?
我们要找海妖什么的吗
We lookin' for some kind of siren or what?
不是那么回事  好了
No. Nothing like that. All right, um...
这事有点突然
So, a little sudden.
不过人生苦短  我就长话短说
But life is short, so I'll keep this shorter.
我恋爱了
I'm in love.
而且我要结婚了
And I'm getting married.
说点什么啊
Say something, like, uh,
像是"恭喜你"之类的
like, "Congratulations," for example.
什么
What?
搞什么飞机
What the hell?
贝基
Becky?
迪恩
Dean.
很高兴你能来
I'm so glad you're here.
[邪恶力量 第7季第8集]
难道她不应该征得我的同意吗
Shouldn't she ask for my permission or something?
你想让她向你提亲吗
Y-you want her to ask for my hand?
你们是...
How in the --
你们怎么走到一起的
how did this happen?
长话短说
Short version?
我们...  我们相遇
We -- we -- we met.
我们吃饭  聊天  然后相爱了
We ate and -- and talked and fell in love.
然后就走到这一步了
And, you know, here we are.
好吧  我基本上了解了
Yeah, I-I guess I'm all caught up.
好吧
That's -- okay.
你猜怎么着  先不管别的
You know what? Ignoring everything...
难道你忘了  你钓的马子都活不长吗
Have you forgotten the average life-span of your hookups?
记得  但...
Yeah, but --
但最了解情况的人  莫过于我了
But if anyone knows that, it's me.
我每本书都读过
I mean, I read every book.
所以我完全理解
So, open eyes, you know?
理解万岁
Open eyes.
我快要吐了
I'm gonna be sick.
迪恩  事情很简单
Dean, look, it's simple.
幸福来了  我得抓紧
I-if something good's happening, I-I got to jump on it --
抓住今时今日
Now, today, period.
给我玩《死亡诗社》
Okay, "Dead poets society." fine.
无意冒犯  不过你确定她不是什么...
No offense -- did you make sure she's even really --
盐  圣水  什么都用过
Salt, holy water, everything.
看
See?
我不是怪物
Not a monster.
只是你弟弟的真命天女
Just the right girl for your brother.
仅此而已
That's it.
请付账
The bill.
我来吧
I got it.
你们哥俩好好聊聊
You two do your brother thing.
你丫抽风吧  竟然娶了头号粉丝
Really?! Superfan ninety-nine?!
迪恩  听着
Dean, look.
说心里话  我以前对她的看法和你完全一样
Honest to god, I-I had the exact same opinion of her as you do.
但是除了书的事
But when we got past the whole book thing,
我发现她很好  是我太混蛋
I found out t-that she's great and I was the dick.
好吧  既然说到了书的事情
Yeah, you know, speaking of the whole, uh, book thing...
贝基只是碰巧在维加斯出现吗
Becky randomly shows up during Vegas week?
是啊
Yeah.
是吧
好吧  你究竟想说什么
Okay, um, what are you trying to say?
我想说她可能早就知道你要来这儿
I'm saying maybe she knew you were gonna be here.
也许  恰克写下来了
Maybe, uh, uh, uh, Chuck wrote about it.
-迪恩  你想多了  -你还爱上她了
- Dean, you're paranoid. - And you're in love?!
才四天时间啊  哥们
It's been four days, man!
这样  别激动  迪恩
You know what, Dean? You know what?
你听我说
Um, how about this?
贝基准备带我去她在特拉华州的住处
Becky and I are gonna go up to her place in Delaware.
你不如把这事想通了
Um, why don't you try and wrap your dome around this,
给我们更多支持  然后打给我们
get a little supportive, then give us a call?
身为贝基·罗森·温彻斯特太太
"First official tweet
所发的第一条正式微博
as Mrs. Becky Rosen-Winchester."
鲍比  我知道你在俄勒冈的老巢里焦头烂额
Bobby. Hey, I know you're, uh, beard-deep in that Oregon nest.
我要去特拉华州做些调查
I am headed to Delaware to do a little snoop around.
萨姆和他老婆在那儿
Sam is there with his wife.
真的  你没听错  他老婆
That's right. You heard me. His wife.
打给我
Call me.
(特拉华州  派克河)
(新婚  2001届毕业生  欢迎来到)
不是刚吃过了吗
I thought we just ate.
很快就好
Quick stop.
那是我的错吗
Well, is that my fault?
我都告诉你多少遍了  我们有票
I told you we had tickets 11 times.
嗨  乔斯林
Hi, Jocelyn.
我再打给你吧
Let me call you back.
找个保姆  多大点事儿
Just get a sitter. It's not calculus.
你好  有什么能帮你的
Yes. Can I help you?
我是贝基·罗森
It's Becky. Becky Rosen.
大嘴贝基
"Yechie Becky."
好早的事儿了
Ha. Long time ago.
大嘴贝基
Yechie Becky!
你看起来没变样儿啊  对吧
Well, you look just the same, don't you?
我是来登记参加同学聚会的
I'm here to R.S.V.P. for the reunion,
希望不会太晚
if it's not too late.
当然不会  多个人从来就不是问题
No, no, there is always room for one more.
其实呢
Actually...
是温彻斯特夫妇
It's Rosen-Winchester.
请帮我写"带家属"
So mark me down "Plus one."
搞定乔斯林·卡罗索
"Jocelyn Caruso roasted."
嗨  盖
Hi, Guy!
你回来了
You're back!
维加斯怎么样
How was Vegas?
酷毙了
It was awesome!
真的吗  不开玩笑
Really? Really?
盖
Guy...
见过我的老公
meet my husband...
萨姆
Sam.
你好
Hey.
很荣幸见到你  萨姆
It's an honor to meet you, sam.
谢谢  我也是
Thanks. You too.
盖是我的好朋友
Guy's a really good friend.
我们在小说店的色情恐怖文学区认识的
We met in the erotic horror section at the novel hovel.
上帝啊  贝基  饶了我吧
Oh, my god, Becky. Come on!
说太多了
T.M.I.
人家第一次见面嘛
Poor guy's just met me.
没关系的  很高兴见到你
No, it's okay. Nice to meet you.
要知道  只要是贝基的朋友
Look, any friend of Becky's...
好吧  我该去干活了
Anyway, I should, uh, get back to it,
否则这次聚会就泡汤了
or this party's not gonna happen, right?
当然
Sure.
盖负责活动策划
Guy's an event planner.
每到同学聚会总有他忙的
Reunion season is very busy for him.
等我一下
Hold on one sec?
还有一件事
One more thing.
收到我的消息没
You get my message?
当然  我还以为你不会问呢
Of course. I thought you'd never ask.
抱抱我
Give me a hug.
说真的  如果人人口袋里都有巫士
I swear, if everyone had a wiccan in their pocket,
这个世界就快乐多了
the world would be a happier place.
小菜一碟
It is nothing.
祝你好运  亲爱的
Blessed be, sweetie.
(诡异事故  卡车碾死行人  死者不久前彩票中奖)
你很漂亮
Wow. Y-you look n-nice.
谢谢
Thanks!
我一直留着
I was, you know...
没舍得穿
saving it.
为我们干杯
To us.
萨姆  你没事吧
Sam? Are you okay?
亲爱的小萨姆  你怎么了
Sammy, honey, what's wrong?
贝基  我怎么在...
Becky? W-why am I...
我在这儿干嘛
What am I doing here?
我们在庆祝啊  亲爱的
We're celebrating, dear.
想起来了吗
Remember?
没错  当然了
Yeah, yeah, of course.
为我们干杯
To us.
感觉好些了吗  亲爱的
Feeling better, honey?
有你在身边就好
Now that I'm with you.
支持你来了
Me being supportive.
祝你和太太新婚快乐
Congratulations to you and the missus.
谢谢
Thanks.
这是松饼机  不粘锅的
It's a waffle iron. Nonstick.
你只需要  你知道...
Yeah, you just, uh, you know...
其实我不懂怎么用  我们算和好了吗
I actually don't know how to use it. Are we good?
那好  我觉得这镇上有案子
Good, 'cause I'm sniffing a case in this town.
是这样的
The score is...
有个中了彩票的家伙  被卡车给碾平了
Guy wins powerball, gets squished by a truck...
还有个家伙从替补拼到了主力
Second guy went from the bench to the majors.
一周过后
Oh, and one week later,
他的脸被球砸开花
His face was the catcher's mitt, huh?
我们起先认为是十字路口恶魔
Our first thought was crossroads demons,
但是他们收集灵魂有个十年期限
but there's that 10-year time frame on collecting souls.
还有受诅咒的物件  就像《黑岩喋血记》
Then there's cursed object, like in "Bad day at black rock,"
我们还没有找到死者之间的联系
but we haven't been able to connect the vics yet.
你们正在一起调查这个案子吗
You're working this case... together?
没错  可不是嘛
Yeah. I know. Right?
恰克·雪利的书总算是没白写
I mean, I guess all those Chuck Shurley books paid off.
好吧  听着  小可爱
All right, listen, cookie,
我不知道你在玩什么把戏
I don't know what kind of mojo you're working,
但请你相信  我一定能查出来
but, believe me, I will find out.
迪恩  不要这样跟我老婆说话
Dean, that's...my wife you're talking to.
你的表现太异常了  萨姆
You're not even acting like yourself, Sam!
怎么异常
How am I not?
你娶了贝基·罗森
You married Becky Rosen!
你说什么呢
What are you saying?
我是女巫吗
I'm a witch?
还是海妖
Or maybe I'm a siren.
你就没想过  我们只是很幸福吗
Ever occur to you we're just -- I don't know -- happy?!
拜托了  萨姆
Come on, sam!
又是中乐透  又是功成名就的
Guy wins the lotto, guy hits the bigs.
再明显不过了
All right, obviously,
在这镇上  人人都梦想成真了
uh, people's dreams are coming true in this town.
你就不觉得这未免太巧合了吗
Don't you think this is a little bit of a coincidence?
够了  迪恩
You know what, Dean?
贝基和我绝对是真情所致
What Becky and I have is real.
你接受不了
And if you can't accept that,
是你的问题  绝非我们
That's your problem, not ours.
或许她也有份
Or maybe she's part of it.
种种迹象都表明  你正是她的梦中情人
Because for whatever reason, you're her dream.
如果你真心在意她  就该担心她
If you really do care about her, I'd be worried.
因为那些美梦成真  得偿所愿的家伙
Because people who do get their little fantasies or whatever
似乎都立刻死翘翘了
seem to end up dead pretty quick.
迪恩  也许你之所以无法接受
You know, I went after her, Dean.
是因为我与贝基结了婚
Maybe that's what's bugging you --
我开始了自己的生活
that I'm moving on with my life.
我知道你一直照顾我  那很好
I mean, you took care of me, and that's great.
但我已不再需要你了
But I don't need you anymore.
我不需要别的搭档  鲍比  你干嘛不来
I don't want another hunter, Bobby. Why can't you do it?
好吧
Fine.
那家伙叫啥
What's his name?
我给你准备了一份礼物
I got you a present.
小两口的假身份证
His and hers fake I.D.?!
这儿  瞧瞧这篇报道
Here. Check this out.
联合自由保险公司
"Junior salesman leapfrogs to C.E.O.
一名初级销售员跃升为执行总裁
at Mutual Freedom Insurance."
你觉得这个执行总裁是源头吗
You think the C.E.O. is a lead?
贝基
Uh, Becky?
这真是
This is...
太漂亮了
...beautiful.
你怎么看这个执行总裁的事
So, what do you think about the C.E.O.?
咱俩去试探他吧
Let's go pretext him!
你是迪恩吗
Hey. You Dean?
我还以为你会高点儿
Hmm. I thought you'd be taller.
我想鲍比已经将把情况都跟告诉你了吧
I assume Bobby filled you in on the road.
他就告诉了我两件事
He told me two things.
一  他现在正忙着在俄勒冈州大地上建立大本营
One, he's tangling with a major-league nest up in Oregon territory.
其次
Numero dos,
提到了你
he said you'd be all, uh,
对跟我公事的事有点经前狂躁
surly and premenstrual working with me.
不过  伙计  说说而已  别受伤
But, hey, man, sticks and stones.
我发现了件案子
Think I found a case.
瞧瞧标题
Check the headline.
重要的先做
First thing's first.
马默杜克  真够疯狂的
Oh, Marmaduke, you're crazy!
你这是在侮辱我吗
Are you trying to humiliate me?
是草字头的莎  玛莎
It's Marsha with an "S-H-A,"
而不是只有三点水的
Not a "C-I-A."
再次谢谢你
Thanks again.
-那是你的...  -没错
- Hey, is that your -- - Yes.
真尴尬
Awkward.
好吧
Okay.
怎么样
So...
没必要进去了  毫无异样
So, uh, no point in going in. Guy's clean.
你确定
You sure?
是的  绝对的  贝基拷问起来完全专业
Yeah. Positive. Becky grilled him like a pro.
她简直就是个天才
She's a real natural.
这个瘦皮猴是干嘛的
W-what's with the scrawny guy?
临时搭档
Temp.
现在真是扔一块石头也能砸着个记者啊
Throw a rock, hit a reporter these days, eh?
我们很重视你的故事...
Well, your story's a big deal over at the, uh,
我们《真实内幕》很看重
the Actuarial Insider.
好吧  问吧
Go ahead. Shoot.
好的
All right.
你怎么得到机会的
Uh... How'd you get the gig?
董事会找到我  问我是否愿意  我当然说愿意啦
Board came to me, asked. Said yes.
就这么突然
Just out of the blue?
确实
Pretty much.
想过董事会为什么会找上你
Huh. And, uh, any idea how the board landed on you
甚至跳过了你的上级
over your supervisors?
他们没提过
Um, they didn't say.
那你能说说你自身有什么实力
Could you tell us what specifically excited the board
能让董事会这么钟情于你呢
about your actual qualifications?
嘿  两位  你们这么刨根问底是要干嘛
Say, fellas, what's with the third degree?
哦  请别见怪
Oh, uh, no offense.
我们只想知道你究竟用了什么歪门邪道
We were just wondering if you got here by nefarious means.
盖思
Garth!
我当然不是那意思
Uh, I-I didn't mean, of course, uh,
不是指暗箭伤人之类的  抱歉
corporate backstabbing -- I'm sorry.
我想说的是
I meant more like,
黑魔法啊或是巫毒术之类的
Uh, you know, black magic or hoodoo.
开玩笑的  他就是  就是喜欢开玩笑
He jokes. He's a -- he's a jokester.
我们  还是回到正题上来
Let's, uh, rewind.
不如  不如你说说
Why don't, uh, why don't you tell us
自己梦想成真的感觉吧
what it felt like when your big dream came true?
官方说法的话  感觉棒极了
Look, on the record, it's great.
私下来说呢
Off the record?
这不算是我梦寐以求的
It's not my big dream.
等下  你不想要这份工作吗
Wait. You didn't want this job?
该死的  不想  我就是个售货员
Hell, no. I'm a sales guy.
我擅长卖东西
I was good in sales.
你的秘书真是个二货
Your secretary's an idiot.
下午我去印刷商那边
I'll be at the printers this afternoon.
好的  亲爱的  一起吃晚餐
All right, Dear. See you at dinner.
那就叫那个二货预定好餐厅
Just have the idiot make a reservation.
不如这样  提醒她  她可是执行总裁秘书
Here's a tip -- remind her she works for the C.E.O.
再搞砸了  就让她卷铺盖走人
One more screw-up, she's fired.
你太太对你的晋升似乎很激动啊
Your, uh, wife seems pretty stoked on the promotion, don't she?
说实话  我从没见她这么开心过
Honestly, I've never seen her happier.
我不知道怎么告诉她我不得不辞职的事
I have no idea how I'm gonna tell her I have to resign.
-这个消息一定会  -打击死她
- The news is just gonna -- - Kill her?
巴罗斯太太  你好
Mrs. Burrows? Hi.
有何贵干
Can I help you?
我们要作一篇你丈夫晋升的报道
Yes, we're, uh, we're doing a story on your husband's promotion.
也想采访一下你
Wanted to ask you a few questions.
抱歉  今天不行  先跟他秘书预约吧
I'm sorry. I can't today. If you schedule it with his girl...
好吧  你知道吗
Okay, you know what?
我是想帮你免遭可怕意外的厄运
I'm trying to save you from a really bad accident.
你是在威胁我吗
Are you threatening me?
不
No.
不是  我只是指出一个规律
No, I-I'm pointing out a pattern.
为什么总是有人觉得我是在威胁他们呢
Why do people keep thinking I'm threatening them?
因为那听起来确实就像威胁  伙计
Because it sounded exactly like a threat, dude.
听着  这是为了你好
Look, for your own good,
你动了什么手脚让他升职
what did you do to get him promoted?
我完全不懂你在说什么
I have no idea what you're talking about.
现在别再来烦我了
Now leave me alone.
否则我就打电话叫保安了
Or do I have to call security?
不  不 不  有什么被遗漏了
No, no, no, something's not adding up.
我敢肯定我们会时来运转的
I'm sure we'll get a break.
一旦结束了手上的案子
"As soon as we're done working,
浪漫的蜜月就将展开
romantic honeymoon getaway."
把车开过来
Bring the damn car around.
我可不想踩着高跟鞋走五个街区
I'm not walking five blocks in my heels.
你没事吧
You okay?
你怎么会知道的
How did you know?
因为你并不是第一个  来吧
'cause you're not the first. Come on.
你想告诉我们这是怎么回事吗
You want to tell us what's up here?
我在跟朋友吃饭
I was having lunch with friends.
这个人听到我抱怨
This guy heard me bitching.
接下来他就向我提出了一个提议
Next thing I know, he's making me an offer.
什么提议
An offer?
用我的灵魂换克雷格的工作
Craig's job for my soul.
我知道很滑稽  我有什么可以失去的呢
I know. Hilarious. I mean, what have I got to lose?
你的灵魂啊
Well, there's your soul.
这算什么恶魔交易  期限很奇怪
What kind of demon deal is this? Timeline's wack.
你们在说什么  恶魔
What are you talking about? "Demon"?
我来说下背景资料
Let me back up here.
你跟恶魔做交易  以不灭的灵魂换取愿望
You made a deal with a demon in exchange for your everlasting.
不过那些都是十年期的合同
Except those are 10-year contracts.
为什么这么快就来收账了呢
Why's the bill coming due so fast?
不知道  但我对下一个是谁有不祥预感
I don't know, but I got a bad feeling about who's next.
我们得找到萨姆  要快
We got to find Sam, pronto.
好吧  好吧  好吧  计划是这样的
All right, all right, all right. Uh, here's the plan.
我把这位女士送到我表兄家
I drop this lady at my cousin's.
他会阻止任何想要接近她的东西
He'll stop anything trying to get her.
我们去找萨姆  希望能收拾好这烂摊子
We, uh, find Sam, hopefully fix this,
大家就都能及时赶回家看《美国达人》了
everybody's home in time for "America's got talent".
好了  你要跟一个  截瘫的狙击手一起住
Now, you -- you'll be living with a triracial paraplegic sniper
直到这事结束  知道吗
until this all blows over, okay?
盖  你在哪里
Guy, where are you?
我们要马上见个面
We need to meet up, fast!
我在失去萨姆
I'm losing Sam.
贝基
Becky...
怎  怎么  怎么回事
W-what's -- what's happening?
你不记得了吗  我们结婚了
Don't you remember? We're married.
天...
Oh, g--
我要打电话给迪恩
I'm calling Dean.
萨姆  你有没有觉得有点脑震荡
Sam, do you feel concussion-y?
我举了几根手指
How many fingers am I holding up?
我在哪里  怎么回事
Where am I? What the hell's going on?
萨姆  冷静
Sam... Just calm down.
冷静  你把我绑在
Calm down?! You hogtied me t--
贝基  我  我为什么没穿裤子
Becky, why -- why am I not wearing any pants?
裤子太勒了
They're very constricting.
别担心  我没做什么奇怪的事
Don't worry. I didn't do anything weird.
我在帮忙
I was helping.
马上放了我
Let me go. Now!
你渴吗
Are you thirsty?
还是你需要一个瓶子
Or do you need a bottle...
来  撒尿吗
to, you know, tinkle?
如果你要的话也没关系  我可以帮忙
It's okay if you do. I can help.
终于来了
Finally!
等等  什么情况  贝基  不要
Wait. What? Wait. Becky? Becky. Hey, hey, don't!
不要  贝基
Don't! Becky!
你上哪里去了
Where have you been?!
我收到你的信息了  有麻烦吗
I got your messages. Problem?
大麻烦
Big problem.
我在我父母的小屋里
I'm at my parents' cabin.
我把萨姆绑在床上
I've got Sam tied to a bed.
我没有魔法药水了  再给我一点
I'm out of elixir. I need a refill, okay?
这可不是我想要的蜜月
This isn't the honeymoon I had in mind.
一部分是  但不是这个样子的
Well, some of it is, but not in this context.
难道只有我觉得
And is it just me, or is
这东西真的消耗得越来越快了
this stuff wearing off faster and faster?!
贝基  深呼吸
Becky...breathe.
你知不知道我们还没有圆房呢
Do you know we haven't even consummated our marriage?
我们慢慢来是因为真爱是永恒的
We were taking it slow 'cause true love is forever,
但现在一切都感觉好奇怪
but everything just feels weird now.
好吧  我们一个小时后见
All right. Meet me in an hour.
你给我吃了爱情魔药
So you dosed me with a love potion.
-你怎么  -隔墙有耳
- How -- - Thin walls.
没错  我是用了社交润滑剂来
Yes, I used a social lubricant to --
你给我下药
You roofied me!
下药  我绝对不会
A roofie? I'd never.
我们在一起很快乐
We had a great time together.
你很快乐
You were happy.
没错  我很激动
Oh, yeah. I'm thrilled.
我得走了
I have to go.
你知道是盖杀了那些人吧
You know your pal Guy is the one icing all those people, right?
不  不是他
No, he's not.
难道他不是巫师吗
Oh, so he's not a witch?
不是
No.
他只是个巫士
He's just a wiccan.
巫士都是好人  就像《奥兹国的格琳达》
Wiccans are good, like Glinda of Oz.
贝基  你不是这么傻吧
You're not this stupid, Becky.
无论是什么在杀人
Whatever is killing people...
一定是别的东西
it's something else.
从来都没有别的东西
It's never something else.
什么时候有过一个镇上发生两件怪事啊
When are there ever two crazy things in town at the same time?
盖不是好东西  而你也要被他宰了
Guy's the creep, and you're on his list.
不  他是我朋友
No. He's my friend.
不  他是你的交易人
No, he's your dealer.
我不知道
Look, I don't know
他以什么为回报卖你欧芫菁的
how much he's charging you for that spanish fly --
什么都没有  他送给我的
Nothing! He gives it to me.
而且他说如果不是你内心深处
And he said it wouldn't even work
早已爱上我的话  这东西是不会管用的
unless you already loved me, deep down.
这东西不过是把你的爱激发出来
It just activates it.
你觉得我爱你
So you think I love you?
或许在内心深处
Deep, deep down?
那就给我松绑
Then untie me.
不  别
No. No!
你还在整理你的感情
You're still working through your emotions.
我也爱你
I love you, too!
(欢迎来到2001届毕业生十年聚会)
放在桌上  就在名牌边上
On the table, next to the nametags.
盖
Guy.
不如坐下再说
Why don't you take a seat?
今天不顺吗
Tough day?
好吧
Okay.
如果你想  我们就直奔主题
We can cut right to it if you like.
我们来谈谈价钱
Let's talk price.
什么
What?
你不觉得我们已经有点过了免费赠品的阶段了
Well, we're a little past the freebie stage, don't you think?
但我以为我们是闺蜜
But I thought we were besties.
亲爱的
Ohh, honey.
还真是"贝基"的让人郁闷啊
That is so depressingly "Becky."
你也太可悲了
I mean, it's -- you're so pathetic,
可悲到可爱了
it actually loops back around again to cute.
好吧  你要我付钱  可以
Okay. You want me to pay, fine.
你接受个人支票吗
Do you accept personal checks?
不接受
No.
但我接受你的灵魂
But I will take your soul.
你是个十字路口恶魔
You're a crossroads demon.
答对了
Bingo, bango!
我喜欢同学聚会
I love reunions.
那种绝望
The desperation!
那帮蠢货会为了金钱  权利  头发
These schlubs will sign on the dotted line
而跟我交易
for money, power, hair --
不惜一切代价给当年
Whatever it takes to impress
光鲜夺目的啦啦队长留下好印象
the nostalgically bangable head cheerleader.
萨姆是对的
Sam was right.
是你杀了那些人
You killed those people.
可是从法律上看
But for legal reasons,
我们只说他们遭遇了...
let's just say they had...
不幸的意外事故
unfortunate accidents.
那是怎样  我交出自己的灵魂
So, what, I hand over my soul,
明天就会有一台钢琴砸我头上
and the next day a piano falls on my head?
不  我才不会那样对你
No, I'd never do that to you.
我保证
I promise.
我又不傻
I'm not stupid.
可你很特别
But you are special.
是吗
I am?
你的新丈夫是怪人萨姆·温彻斯特
I wasn't thrilled to see your new hubby
这对我不是好消息
was Sam freakin' Winchester.
如果他知道
I mean, if he knew
我现在和你说这些  他很可能
that I was here talking to you, I mean, he'd probably --
-爆你的菊  -就是
- Gank your ass. - Yes!
我可是对我的小菊花保护有加的
And I'm very protective of my ass.
是我最漂亮的地方之一了
It's one of my best features.
贝基  我准备给你提供一份一次性交易
Becky, I'm prepared to offer you a one-time-only deal.
不是十年
Not 10 years.
是二十五
25.
不会用钢琴砸你  我保证
No pianos, guaranteed.
只有萨姆
Just Sam.
拿走我的灵魂
For my soul.
你还需要保证不会向温彻斯特兄弟
And your promise to not breathe a word about this
透露只字片语
to the winchesters,
那我就屁颠屁颠地走人
And I'll be on my merry way.
没人得到过这么好的交易  贝基
No one gets a deal like this, Becky.
国王  教皇都没有过
Not kings, not popes.
我只需一弹指
I snap my fingers,
萨姆在你的余生都会爱着你
and Sam will love you for the rest of your life.
我现在想喝一杯了
I think I'll have that drink now.
有什么吗
Anything?
她发了十一条微博
Uh, she's got 11 twitter...ers.
最后一条
Last post --
"踏上与老公的浪漫之旅"
"Going on romantic trip with Hubster!!!"
打了三个感叹号
Three exclamation points.
我猜她应该很兴奋
I guess she got excited.
你觉得这看起来浪漫吗
That look romantic to you?
当然不了
Oh, hell, no.
但我个人而言不喜欢鱼
But I got this thing about fish.
死鱼眼
Dead eyes, man.
我心中的同学聚会可不是这个样子
This is not how I imagined spending my reunion.
我本想带着你四处炫耀
I was gonna show you off --
当然不能让别人知道你的真实身份
Not that anyone actually knows who you are.
《凶鬼恶灵》现在已经不火了  可是...
"Supernatural" is not exactly popular, but...
你如此的高大...
You're tall...
和气...
and nice and...
他们都会认为我过得很幸福
...they'd all think I was happy.
你生我气  我知道
You're mad. I get it.
可是...
But...
我们能谈谈么
can we talk?
我知道你不爱我
I know you don't love me.
我有自知之明
I know what I am, okay?
我就是个失败者
I'm a loser.
不管是在学校还是在生活中
In school, in life.
我想这也是为什么我会这么喜欢你
Guess that's why I like you so much.
啥
What?!
不是说你是个失败者
I mean, not that you're a loser,
但是你具备成为一个怪胎的
but you had that whole character arc
所有的品质特征
about being a freak, and...
而我都能理解
I can relate.
说真的...
Honestly...
唯一能让人们理解我的地方
the only place people understood me
就是留言板了
was the message boards.
虽然都是些暴躁且偏激的文字
They were grumpy and overly literal,
但至少我们有共同的喜好
but at least we shared a common passion.
我乐在其中  你知道吗
And I'll take it, you know?
直到我遇到了你们
Then I met you guys --
如假包换的萨姆和迪恩
The real Sam and Dean.
我开始和恰克约会
And I started dating Chuck.
这一切的一切
And everything was...
太美妙了
amazing.
可是你们离开了
But you left,
恰克也把我甩了
and Chuck dumped me.
我想是我旺盛的性欲把他吓坏了
I think I intimidated him with my vibrant sexuality.
我只是希望有人能爱真正的我
I just want someone who loves me for me!
这要求很过分吗
Is that too much to ask?
说什么
What?
如果你希望有人爱真正的你
If you want somebody to love you for you,
就别给他们下药
maybe don't drug them.
可我想要你
But I want you!
这也是唯一的办法
And this is the only way!
贝基
Becky.
贝基  你不是这种人
Becky, you're better than this.
嘴真甜  可是...
That's sweet, but...
我不是很确定
I'm not so sure.
贝基
Becks!
你错过派对了
You missed the party.
是的
Yeah. Well...
今晚真奇怪
Weird night.
你什么打算
So, what are we thinking?
好吧
Okay.
我同意
I'm in.
你的决定是对的
You're making the right choice.
我知道
I know.
那...
So...
我们接个吻就搞定了吗
We seal the deal with a kiss?
就是这样
Exactly.
嘴撅起来  甜心
Pucker up, sweetheart.
我才不是你的甜心
I'm not your sweetheart!
蓝莓味的伏特加
Blueberry vodka.
为您解决一切生活烦恼
The answer to all of life's problems.
你看到了吗
You see that, Sam?!
我按我们说的做了
I did it just like we said!
我真是太牛叉了  我
I am awesome! I --
我就待在这
I'll be over here.
迪恩·温彻斯特
Dean Winchester.
真是让人太兴奋了
This is really thrilling.
能给我签个名吗
Hey, can I have your autograph?
当然了
Sure.
我会  把它刻在你的脾脏上
Yeah, I'll, uh, carve it into your spleen.
你是怎么操作你那套小把戏的
So, how you running your little scam?
你在说什么呢  迪恩
Well, how do you mean, Dean?
签署十年条约  把他们的灵魂吸走
Signing 10-year deals, snuffing 'em that week.
我从没做过  没有
Well, I would never. No.
道上的规矩
Rules of the road --
不能伤害我的客户
can't lay a hair on any of my clients.
好吧  那你怎么作弊的
Right. So how you cheating it?
我不是骗子  我是革新者
I'm not a cheater. I'm an innovator.
这叫钻空子  你个傻逼
It's called a loophole, you moron.
是的  当一个人出售自己的灵魂
Yes, when a person bargains away his soul,
按理说  他有十年时间
he gets a decade, technically.
意外时有发生
But accidents happen.
你安排这些"意外"然后再提前收集灵魂
So you're arranging "accidents" and collecting early?
拜托  我的手很干净
Oh, please. White gloves.
这种事不用脏了我的手
I don't get my hands dirty.
因此有一个能干的实习生是很重要的
That's why it's important to have a capable intern.
我叫你什么时候来的
What time did I ask you to be here?!
[咒语]
贝基  快跑
Becky...run!
麦道夫(庞氏骗局策划者)  你在这镇上做了多少交易
How many deals you got cooking in this town, Madoff?
十五笔
15.
都取消
Yeah, well, call them off,
不然我就在你喉咙上钻个空子
or I'll cut my own loophole in your throat.
糟糕
Oh, crap.
对  你说的对  你现在就...
Yeah, you said it. You're in a world --
孩儿们好
Hello, boys.
糟糕
Oh, crap.
萨姆  恭喜  那位幸运的女士是谁
Sam, mazel tov. Who's the lucky lady?
你是克劳力
You're Crowley!
而你
And you're --
亲爱的  我相信你一定很有人格魅力
Well, I'm sure you have a wonderful personality, dear.
再上前一步
Ah, another step,
我就在你这位朋友喉咙上划一刀
and I'll colombian necktie your little friend here.
拜托  别让他死得这么容易
Please, don't let him get off that easy.
先生  我觉得你不
Sir, I don't think that you --
我清楚知道你都干了些什么
I know exactly what you've been doing.
一个叫杰克逊的小鸟已经把你给卖了
A little birdie named Jackson sold you out,
把你那些丑事都发电邮到我的意见箱里了
e-mailed all the juicy deets to my suggestion box.
我猜
I assume...
那就是我的告密人了
that's my whistle-blower?
真可惜  还有大好前途呢
Shame. Had a future.
不幸的是  你就没有了
Unfortunately, you don't.
-我只是  -只有一个规矩
- I was just -- - There's only one rule --
做了交易  就要遵守
make a deal, keep it.
严格说来  我没有
Well, technically, I didn't --
我们不提前收账是有原因的
There's a reason we don't call our chits in early --
消费者信心
consumer confidence.
这不是华尔街  而是地狱
This isn't Wall Street! This is hell!
我们还是要讲诚信的
We have a little something called integrity.
没有诚信  谁来跟我们交易  没人了
This gets out, who'll deal with us? Nobody!
那我们怎么办
Then where are we?!
我不知道
I don't know.
没错  你是不知道
That's right. You don't.
因为你是个愚蠢而又鄙陋的傻子
Because you're a stupid, shortsighted little prat.
现在  把这蠢货交给我
Now, hand the jackass over.
我会取消他每一笔交易
I'll cancel every deal he's made.
你要拿他怎么办
What are you gonna do with him?
杀鸡儆猴
Make an example of him.
公平交易  对吧
Fair trade, right?
然后我们就各行其路
We all go our separate ways.
不用造成伤亡
No harm done.
怎么  突然大发善心了
What, out of the goodness of your heart?
多年追杀你的恶魔
Years of demons nipping at your heels,
却已经几个月没见到了  想知道原因吗
haven't seen one for months. Wonder why?
我们忙着呢
We've been a little busy.
猎杀利维坦  我知道
Hunting Leviathan -- yes, I know.
因此我叫小的们别去碍你们两个笨蛋的眼
That's why I told my lads to stay clear of you meatheads.
那你知道
So, what do you know about --
太多了  你们见过那家伙了吗
Too much. You met that dick yet?
自墨索里尼(意大利法西斯党首领)以来最自命不凡的一桶粘液
Smuggest tub of goo since Mussolini.
我讨厌那帮王八蛋
I hate the bastards.
拜托把他们都灭了吧
Squash 'em all, please.
我就不来碍事了
I'll stay clear.
先撕毁合同再说
Rip up the contracts first.
搞定  统统搞定
Done...and done.
该你们了
Your turn.
不  不  不要  让
No, no, no, no. Let --
很乐意  绅士们
Pleasure, gentlemen.
我都错过什么了
What'd I miss?
也
It...
也没有很糟吧
It wasn't all bad, right?
你  你确实救了我的命
Okay, y-you did save my life,
为了那个  谢了
and for that, thanks.
那我们还会见面吗
So, I'll see you again?
可能不会了
Yeah, probably not.
贝基
Becky, look.
你不是个失败者  好吗
You're not a loser, okay?
你是个好人  你还有
You're a good person, a-and you've got...
很有
A lot of...
活力
e-energy.
做好自己的事  无论是什么事
So, you know, just do your thing, whatever that is,
你命中注定的那个人一定会找到你的
and the right guy will find you.
不
No.
不行
兄弟  我不得不说
Well, buddy, I got to say, man --
你  你还挺不错的
you, uh... you don't suck.
谢谢你
Thank you.
那是人家跟我说的最中听的一句话了
That's the nicest thing anyone's ever said to me.
好吧  这个
Yeah. All right, that's --
谢谢你
Thank you.
保重
Take care.
你交了个朋友呢
Aw, you made a friend.
听着
Look, man, uh...
我被下药的时候  说了些乱七八糟的话
...when I was all dosed up, I-I said some crap.
你是说  她  她不是你的灵魂伴侣吗
Oh, you mean, she -- she wasn't your soul mate?
闭嘴
Shut up.
我是说  我确实需要你照顾我
I mean, I do need you watching my back.
这很显然
Obviously.
没错  当疯狂的粉丝来袭之时
Yeah, when, uh, crazy groupies attack.
你懂我的意思的
You know what I mean.
我不得不说
You know, I got to say, man...
作为一个疯子  你真的很振作了
for a wackjob, you really pulled it together.
那是人家跟我说的最中听的一句话了
That's the nicest thing anyone's said to me.
别太感动了
Look, don't be too impressed, man.
我脑子里还是挺乱的
It's still a Denver scramble up here.
现在才刚有点清醒
I just know my way around the plate now.
我就是想说
I'm just saying.
你觉得你一直需要我在身边是很蠢的
It's stupid to think that you need me around all the time.
你是个大人了
You're a grown-up.
没错
Right.
你是个沙漠独行  嬉皮二货型的大人
You're a hike-in-the-desert, hippie-douche grown-up.
兄弟  我在露营  你也露营的
Dude, I was camping. You camp.
随便了  嬉皮士
Yeah, whatever. Hippie.
你知道吗  一本正经说
You know what, though? Seriously?
-可能挺不错的  -什么
- It might be nice. - What?
你基本上整个人生
I mean, you basically have been looking out for me
都是在照顾我
Your whole life.
现在你终于有机会照顾自己了
Now you finally get to take care of yourself.
也是时候了  对吧
About time, huh?
对
Yeah.
没错
Right.